<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Abaresk's Blog</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content on Abaresk's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 22:23:46 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Music</title><link>http://localhost:1313/music/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 22:23:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/music/</guid><description>Surf theme
Your browser does not support the audio element.</description></item><item><title>Trainers Steal Your Pokémon</title><link>http://localhost:1313/mods/pokemon/trainers-steal-your-pokemon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 22:39:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/pokemon/trainers-steal-your-pokemon/</guid><description>At the start of every battle, opponents randomly take a Pokémon from your party and add it to their team.
Difficulty Settings Soft: Trainers give you one Pokémon from their team after battle. There&amp;rsquo;s a small chance they return your Pokémon back to you.
Hard: Trainers do not give Pokémon back to you after battle.
Hardcore: Hard, plus the price of Poké Balls increases by $250 Poké Dollars with every gym badge (which makes losing Pokémon more costly).</description></item><item><title>Debugging Gen III Pokémon Games</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/debugging-gen-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 08:08:57 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/debugging-gen-3/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to quickly share my setup for debugging Gen III Pokémon games. This setup has helped me both understand how undocumented parts of the games work and also create the mods on this site. Hopefully sharing this helps others looking to do the same.
This setup is compatible with the pokeruby, pokefirered, and pokeemerald projects on Linux, MacOS, or WSL.
VSCode VSCode offers a great interface for debugging code. The experience is streamlined into the code editor and uses the source code to provide useful context while debugging.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 22:23:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid><description>Hello, welcome to my personal blog! I&amp;rsquo;m mostly using this as a platform to share my hobbies and things that I find interesting. For me, that&amp;rsquo;s mostly games and music, but perhaps it will include random other ventures as well. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy reading :)
For fun, I like to make mods of older video game titles. I&amp;rsquo;ve compiled these under the &amp;ldquo;Mods&amp;rdquo; section of the page. Feel free to take a look and play if any interest you.</description></item><item><title>2-on-1 Battles</title><link>http://localhost:1313/mods/pokemon/2-on-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 22:39:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/pokemon/2-on-1/</guid><description>Trainers can use two Pokémon at once, while you can only use one. Essentially, it is a double battle for the opponent but a single battle for you.
For exta difficulty, there is also a version that prevents moves from hitting multiple targets (e.g. Surf, Earthquake).
Demo Downloads Use a BPS patcher to apply the patch to the ROM file.
2-on-1 battles emerald-2-on-1.bps firered-2-on-1.bps leafgreen-2-on-1.</description></item><item><title>Lead Poké Balls</title><link>http://localhost:1313/mods/pokemon/lead-ball/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 22:39:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/pokemon/lead-ball/</guid><description>Your Poké Balls are made of lead &amp;ndash; your Pokémon are permanently damaged by lead poisoning both in and out of battle. If your Pokémon actually gets poisoned, it takes double damage.
Unlike regular poison, lead poisoning will also affect Steel- and Poison-type Pokémon.
Too easy? Try beating it without using healing items!
Demo Notes You can disable notifications when Pokémon faint in the Options menu.
Downloads Use a BPS patcher to apply the patch to the ROM file.</description></item><item><title>Pokémon Know One Move</title><link>http://localhost:1313/mods/pokemon/one-move/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 22:39:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/pokemon/one-move/</guid><description>Your Pokémon can only know one move at a time. Opponents and wild Pokémon are unaffected.
Demo Downloads Use a BPS patcher to apply the patch to the ROM file.
emerald-one-move.bps firered-one-move.bps leafgreen-one-move.bps</description></item></channel></rss>